Inventory of the Mimi Benzell papers, 1897-1972 (bulk 1930-1972)
University of Wyoming. American Heritage Center.
- Printed Music, Loose Sheets:
  - MY MELANCHOLY BABY, words by Geo. A. Norton and Maybelle E. Watson, music by Ernie Burnett, undated (Box 31)
  - MY REVERIE, by Larry Clinton, undated (Box 31)
  - MY ROMANCE, lyrics by Lorenz Hart, music by Richard Rodgers, 2 copies, undated (Box 31)
  - MY SHIP, words by Ira Gershwin, music by Kurt Weill, undated (Box 31)
  - MY SISTER AND I, words and music by Hy Zaret, Joan Whitney and Alex Kramer, undated (Box 31)
  - MY SOUL IS DARK, music by Arthur H. Gutman, undated (Box 31)
  - MY THOUGHTS ARE ROAMIN' TONIGHT, lyrics by Jimmy Eaton, music by Robert Stolz, undated (Box 31)
  - MY TIME IS YOUR TIME, words by Eric Little, music by Leo Dance, undated (Box 31)
  - MY WHITE KNIGHT, composer unknown, undated (Box 31)
  - MY WHITE KNIGHT, words and music by Robert Campbell, undated (Box 31)
  - MY YIDDISHE MOMME, lyrics by Jack Yellen, music by Jack Yellen and Lew Pollack, undated (Box 31)
  - NATURE BOY, by Eden Ahbenz, undated (Box 31)
  - NEAPOLITAN LOVE SONG, lyrics by Henry Blossom, music by Victor Herbert, undated (Box 31)
  - NEVER, lyrics by Eliot Daniel, music by Lionel Newman, undated (Box 31)
  - NEVER AGAIN, words and music by Noel Coward, undated (Box 31)
  - NEVER FELT BETTER, NEVER HAD LESS, words and music by Abel Baer and Cliff Hess, undated (Box 31)
  - NEVER ON SUNDAY, lyrcis by Billt Towne, music by Manos Hadjidakis, undated (Box 31)
  - NEW BORN, by Norman Dello Joio, undated (Box 31)
  - NEW HAMPSHIRE, music by Alan Thomas, undated (Box 31)
  - THE NEWS GAME, music by Jacques Wolfe, undated (Box 31)
  - A NEW SHADE OF BLUE, by Russ Smith and James Flora, undated (Box 31)
  - NIGHTINGALE, lyrics by Fred Wise, music by Xavier Cugat, undated (Box 31)
  - NIGHT IS FALLING, J. Haydn, undated (Box 31)
  - NIGHT SONG, lyrics by Lee Adams, music by Charles Strouse, undated (Box 31)
  - THE NIGHT IS FILLED WITH MUSIC, by Irving Berlin, undated (Box 31)
  - THE NIGHT THEY INVENTED CHAMPAGNE, words by Alan Jay Lerner, music by Frederick Loewe, 2 copies, undated (Box 31)
  - THE NIGHT WAS MADE FOR LOVE, by Jerome Kern and Otto Harbach, undated (Box 31)
  - NINA, by G.B. Pergolesi, undated (Box 31)
  - NINA BOBO, by Bainbridge Crist, undated (Box 31)
  - NINETTA AND PEPPPINO, arranged by Alexander Aslanoff, undated (Box 31)
  - NINNA NANNA, music by Theodore Carguilo, undated (Box 31)
  - NOBODY CARES IF I'M BLUE, lyrics by Grant Clarke, music by Harry Akst, undated (Box 31)
  - NOBODY'S CHASING ME, lyrics and music by Cole Porter, undated (Box 31)
  - NOBODY MAKES A PASS AT ME, words and music by Harold J. Rome, undated (Box 31)
  - NOBODY'S HEART, lyrics by Lorenz Hart, music by Richard Rodgers, undated (Box 31)
  - NOCHE DE RONDA, by Maria Teresa Lara, 2 copies, undated (Box 31)
  - NOCTURNE, by Samuel Barber, undated (Box 31)
  - NON DIMENTICAR, lyrics by Shelley Dobbins, music by P. G. Redi, 2 copies, undated (Box 31)
  - NO PROPHET I, by S. Rachmaninoff, undated (Box 31)
  - NORWEGIAN ECHO SONG, by W. Thrance, undated (Box 31)
  - NO STAR IS LOST, by Fred Fisher, undated (Box 31)
  - NOTHIN' FOR NOTHIN', lyrics by Dorothy Fields, music by Morton Gould, undated (Box 31)
  - NOTHING LASTS FOREVER, words and music by Oscar Haimo, undated (Box 31)
  - NOTHING IS TOO PERFECT FOR YOU, words and music by Bud Hofmann, undated (Box 31)
  - NOVILLERO, by Maria Teresa Lara, 2 copies, undated (Box 31)
  - NOWHERE GUY, lyrics by Mack Gordon, music by Josef Myrow, undated (Box 31)
  - NOW I LAY ME DOWN TO SLEEP, music by Robert MacGimsey, undated (Box 31)
  - NOW IS THE TIME!, words by Burton Shevelove, music by Perry Lafferty, undated (Box 31)
  - NOW IT CAN BE TOLD, by Irving Berlin, undated (Box 31)
  - NOW SLEEPS THE CRIMSON PETAL, words by Tennyson, music by Rodger Quilter, undated (Box 31)
  - O BEAUTIFUL STAR, by Oscar Wilde and Maurice Baron, undated (Box 31)
  - THE OBLATION, by Karol Rathaus, undated (Box 31)
  - THE OCARINA, words and music by Irving Berlin, undated (Box 31)
  - O DOCE NOME DE VOCE, music by Francisco Mignone, undated (Box 31)
  - O'ER THE HILLS AND FAR AWAY, by Francis Hopkinson, undated (Box 31)
  - O GATHERING CLOUDS, arranged by K. Marjorie Bain, undated (Box 31)
  - OH DEAR! WHAT CAN THE MATTER BE?, arranged by Arnold Bax, undated (Box 31)
  - OH, HAD I JUBAL'S LYRE, G. F. Handel, undated (Box 31)
  - O HOLY NIGHT!, by Adolphe Adam, undated (Box 31)
  - OH MOTHER MINE, words and music by Pietro Cimini, undated (Box 31)
  - OH, NEVER SING TO ME AGAIN, S. Rachmaninoff, undated (Box 31)
  - OH PROMISE ME, words by Clement Scott, music by Reginald De Koven, undated (Box 31)
  - OH, WHAT A BEAUTIFUL MORNIN', music by Richard Rodgers, lyrics by Oscar Hammerstein II, 2 copies, undated (Box 31)
  - OH, YOU BEAUTIFUL DOLL, words by Seymour Brown, music by Nat D. Ayer, undated (Box 31)
  - OKLAHOMA, words by Oscar Hammerstein II, music by Richard Rodgers, 2 copies, undated (Box 31)
  - AN OLD-FASHIONED GIRLIE, words by James O'Dea, music by Sam S. Krams, undated (Box 31)
  - OLD FOLKS, lyrics by Dedette Lee Hill, music by Willard Robison, undated (Box 31)
  - OLD MILL WHEEL, by Benny Davis, Milton Ager, Jesse Greer, undated (Box 31)
  - OLD SONG, by Douglas Moore, undated (Box 31)
  - THE OLD WOMAN AND THE PEDDLER, arranged by Hazel Gertrude Kinscella, undated (Box 31)
  - O LEGERE HIRONDELLE, arranged by Estelle Liebling, undated (Box 31)
  - OL' JIM, by Clara Edwards, undated (Box 31)
  - O LORD YOU MADE A MOSES, words and music by Robert MacGimsey, undated (Box 31)
  - O MIO BABBINO CARO, English versioon by Anne and Herbert Grossman, 2 copies, undated (Box 31)
  - ON A LITTLE STREET IN SINGAPORE, words by Billy Hill, music by Peter DeRose, undated (Box 31)
  - ON A ROOF IN MANHATTAN, lyrics and music by Irving Berlin, undated (Box 31)
  - ONCE IN A WHILE, words by Bud Green, music by Michael Edwards, undated (Box 31)
  - ONCE UPON A TIME, TODAY, words and music by Irving Berlin, undated (Box 31)
  - ONE ALONE, book and lyrics by Otto Harbach, Oscar Hammerstein II, and Frank Mandel, music by Sigmund Romberg, 3 copies, undated (Box 31)
  - ONE DAY, words and music by Thora Hinshaw Seaton, undated (Box 31)
  - ONE FINE DAY, by G. Puccini, undated (Box 31)
  - ONE HEART WAS YEARNING, by Franz Shubert, arranged by Ann Ronell, undated (Box 31)
  - ONE LITTLE CANDLE, by J. Maloy Roach and George Mysels, undated (Box 31)
  - ONE LOOK AT YOU, by Bart Howard, undated (Box 31)
  - ONE LOVE AFFAIR, by Bart Howard, undated (Box 31)
  - ONE NIGHT OF LOVE, words by Gus Kahn, music by Victor Schertzinger, undated (Box 31)
  - ONE OF THOSE SONGS, English lyrics by Will Holt, music by Gerard Calvi, undated (Box 31)
  - THE ONE ROSE, by Del Lyon and Lani McIntire, undated (Box 31)
  - ONE SONG, words by Larry Morey, music by Frank Churchill, undated (Box 31)
  - ONLY A GLASS OF CHAMPAGNE, words by Arthur Wimperis, music by Noel Gay, undated (Box 31)
  - ONLY A ROSE, lyrics and Brian Hooker, music by Rudolf Friml, undated (Box 31)
  - ONLY WHEN YOU'RE IN MY ARMS, by Con Conrad, Bert Kalmar, and Herman Ruby, undated (Box 31)
  - ONLY YOU, AND YOU ONLY, lyrics by John W. Bratton, music by Mana-Zucca, 2 copies, undated (Box 31)
  - ON THE ROAD TO MANDALAY, words by Rudyard Kipling, music by Oley Speaks, undated (Box 31)
  - ON THIS DAY, words by Hy Zaret, music by Lou Singer, undated (Box 31)
  - ON WINGS OF SONG, arranged by Fred Weber, undated (Box 31)
  - ON YOUR TOES, lyrics by Lorenz Hart, music by Richard Rodgers, undated (Box 31)
  - OPEN THY BLUE EYES, by Jules Massenet, undated (Box 31)
  - O PERFECT LOVE, words by D. F. Blomfield, music by Oscar J. Fox, undated (Box 31)
  - THE OTHER HALF OF ME, music and lyrics by Jack Lawrence and Stan Freeman, undated (Box 31)
  - OUR LANGUAGE OF LOVE, music by Marguerite Monnot, lyrics by Alexandre Breffort, 2 copies, undated (Box 31)
  - OUR LOVE, words and music by Larry Clinton, Buddy Bernier, and Bob Emmerich, undated (Box 31)
  - OUR LOVE AFFAIR, words and music by Arthur Freed and Roger Edens, undated (Box 31)
  - OUR SONG, music by Jerome Kern, lyrics by Dorothy Fields, undated (Box 31)
  - OUT OF MY DREAMS, words by Oscar Hammerstein II, music by Richard Rodgers, undated (Box 31)
  - OVER THE RAINBOW, lyrics by E. Y. Harburg, music by Harold Arlen, 2 copies, undated (Box 31)
  - PAKAD ADONAI ZION, by Zaira and Wolf, undated (Box 32)
  - PALE HANDS I LOVED, words by Laurence Hope, music by Amy Woodforde Finden, undated (Box 32)
  - PAREE WHAT DID YOU DO TO ME, lyrics and music by Cole Porter, undated (Box 32)
  - THE PARISIANS, words by Alan Jay Lerner, music by Frederick Loewe, 2 copies, undated (Box 32)
  - PASSEPIED, transcribed and adapted by Alexander Aslanoff, 2 copies, undated (Box 32)
  - PASTORALE, by Domenico Scarlatti, undated (Box 32)
  - THE PASTURE, by Charles Naginski, undated (Box 32)
  - PAVANNE, by Morton Gould, 2 copies, undated (Box 32)
  - THE PEANUT VENDOR, composed by Moises Simons, undated (Box 32)
  - PENNIES FROM HEAVEN, words by John Burke, music by Arthur Johnson, undated (Box 32)
  - A PENNY FOR YOUR THOUGHTS, words and music by Lee Sims, undated (Box 32)
  - PENNY SERENADE, words by Hal Hallifax, music by Melle Weersma, undated (Box 32)
  - PEOPLE WILL SAY WE'RE IN LOVE, words by Oscar Hammerstein II, music by Richard Rodgers, 2 copies, undated (Box 32)
  - PERHAPS, words by Stephen Sondheim, music by Richard Rodgers, 2 copies, undated (Box 32)
  - THE PHYSICIAN, words and music by Cole Porter, undated (Box 32)
  - THE PICTURE BRIDE, lyrics and music by J. P. Murray, Barry Trivers, Ben Oakland, et al., undated (Box 32)
  - A PICTURE OF ME WITHOUT YOU, music and lyrics by Cole Porter, undated (Box 32)
  - PIGALLE, English lyrics by Charles Newman, music by Georges Ulmer, undated (Box 32)
  - THE PIPER FROM OVER THE WAY, lyrics by Helen Taylor, music by May H. Brahe, undated (Box 32)
  - THE PIPER O'DUNDEE, arranged by Fritz Kreisler, undated (Box 32)
  - PLAIN WE LIVE, lyrics by Arnold B. Horwitt, music by Albert Hague, undated (Box 32)
  - PLAY, FIDDLE, PLAY, lyrics by Jack Lawrence, music by Emery Deutsch and Arthur Altman, undated (Box 32)
  - PLAY GYPSIES-DANCE GYPSIES, music by Emmerich Kalman, undated (Box 32)
  - PLEASE DON'T MAKE ME BE GOOD, lyrics and music by Cole Porter, undated (Box 32)
  - PLEASE NO SQUEEZA DA BANANA, by Louis Prima, Jack Zero, and Ben Jaffe, undated (Box 32)
  - POLLY THE PARROT, words by Lanny Ross, music by Halmy Kresa, undated (Box 32)
  - POOR BUTTERFLY, lyrics by John L. Gold, music by Raymond Hubb, undated (Box 32)
  - POOR PIERROT, by Jerome Kern and Otto Harbach, 2 copies, undated (Box 32)
  - POURQUOI MENTIR, music by Francisico Mignone, undated (Box 32)
  - PRAIRIE SCHOONER, words and music by Harry Pease, Ed G. Nelson, and Billy Haid, undated (Box 32)
  - PRAIRIE WATERS BY NIGHT, muisc by Everett Helm, undated (Box 32)
  - THE PRAISE OF ISLAY, arranged by Fritz Kreisler, undated (Box 32)
  - A PRAYER AT EVENTIDE, music by Reginald King, undated (Box 32)
  - PRAYER OF A WAITING WORLD, words and music by Gene Bone and Howard Fenton, undated (Box 32)
  - THE PRAYER PERFECT, by Oley Speaks, undated (Box 32)
  - PRELUDE TO A KISS, lyrics by Irving Gordon and Irving Mills, music by Duke Ellington, undated (Box 32)
  - PRETTY AS A PICTURE, music by Victor Herbert, lyrics by Robert B. Smith, undated (Box 32)
  - PRIMAVERA, by Celius Dougherty, undated (Box 32)
  - PRIMAVERA D'AMORE, music by Theodore Gargiulo, undated (Box 32)
  - P'S AND Q'S, lyrics by Howard Dietz, music by Johann Strauss, undated (Box 32)
  - PUT IT IN THE BOOK, words and music by Leslie Bricusse and Anthony Newley, undated (Box 32)
  - QUANDO, QUANDO, QUANDO, English words by Pat Boone, music by Tony Renis, 2 copies, undated (Box 32)
  - QUANDO UNA FLOR DESABROCHA, by Francisco Mignone, undated (Box 32)
  - THE QUEEN OF TERRE HAUTE, lyrics and music by Cole Porter, undated (Box 32)
  - QUELQUE-CHOSE, lyrics and music by Cole Porter, undated (Box 32)
  - QUIET NIGHT, music by Richard Rodgers, lyrics by Lorenz Hart, undated (Box 32)
  - QUIET NIGHTS OF QUIET STARS, original words and music by Antonio Carlos Jobim, 2 copies, undated (Box 32)
  - RACHEM, music by Mana-Zucca, undated (Box 32)
  - RAINBOW VALLEY, words by Edgar Leslie, music by Joe Burke, undated (Box 32)
  - RAIN HAS FALLEN, by Samuel Barber, undated (Box 32)
  - RAISINS AND ALMONDS, music and yiddish lyrics by Abraham Goldfaden, 2 copies, undated (Box 32)
  - RAMONA, lyrics by L. Wolfe Gilbert, music by Mabel Wayne, undated (Box 32)
  - RANNOCH, BY GLENCOE, music by Alan Thomas, undated (Box 32)
  - RAPUNZEL, by John Sacco, undated (Box 32)
  - A REAL NICE CLAMBAKE, music by Richard Rodgers, lyrics by Oscar Hammerstein II, undated (Box 32)
  - RECUERDAS TU, by Erneste Lecuona, undated (Box 32)
  - THE RED DRESS, by Mary Margaret Vinmont, undated (Box 32)
  - RED, RED ROSE, by R. L. Cottenet, undated (Box 32)
  - RED ROSEY BUSH, by Victor Young, undated (Box 32)
  - RED SKIES IN THE NIGHT, words and music by Art Noel, Don Hart and Ross Parker, 2 copies, undated (Box 32)
  - REMEMBER, lyrics and music by Irving Berlin, undated (Box 32)
  - REMEMBER ME?, lyrics by Al Dubin, music by Harry Warren, undated (Box 32)
  - RENDEZVOUS TIME IN PAREE, lyrics by Al Dubin, music by Jimmy McHugh, undated (Box 32)
  - REUNION IN WALTZ TIME, words by Florence Tarr, music by Jacques Wolfe, undated (Box 32)
  - THE RHUMBA-CARDI, words and music by Malcolm Eaton and Albert Gamse, undated (Box 32)
  - RIDIN' HIGH, music and lyrics by Cole Porter, undated (Box 32)
  - RIGHT AS THE RAIN, words by E. Y. Harburg, music by Harold Arlen, 2 copies, undated (Box 32)
  - RIGOLETTO, by G. Verdi, undated (Box 32)
  - THE RIVER, words and music by Ann Ronell, undated (Box 32)
  - THE RIVER SEINE, words by Allan Roberts and Alan Holt, music by Guy Lafarge, undated (Box 32)
  - THE ROBIN'S SONG, words by Susan M. Perkins, music by Howard White, undated (Box 32)
  - ROLLING HOME, words and music by Cole Porter, undated (Box 32)
  - ROMANCE, words by Otto Harbach and Oscar Hammerstein II, music by Sigmund Romberg, undated (Box 32)
  - ROMANCE RUNS IN THE FAMILY, words and music by Al Hoffman, Al Goodhart, and Manny Kurtz, undated (Box 32)
  - ROMANY LIFE, lyrics by Harry B. Smith, music by Victor Herbert, undated (Box 32)
  - RONDO ALLA TURCA, by W.A. Mozart, adapted by Alexander Aslanoff, undated (Box 32)
  - THE ROSE ENSLAVES THE NIGHTINGALE, music by N. Rimsky-Korsakov, undated (Box 32)
  - ROSE MARIE, lyrics by Otto Harbach and Oscar Hammerstein II, music by Rudolf Friml, undated (Box 32)
  - ROSE OF THE WORLD, music by Victor Herbert, lyrics by Glen MacDonough, undated (Box 32)
  - ROSE, ROSE, I LOVE YOU, arranged by Chris Langdon, English lyrics by Wilfred Thomas, undated (Box 32)
  - ROSES FROM THE SOUTH, words by Margaret Bristol, arranged by Guiseppe Bamboschej, undated (Box 32)
  - ROSES OF PICARDY, words by Fred E. Weatherly, music by Haydn Wood, undated (Box 32)
  - ROUND ABOUT THE ELFIN RING, arranged by Richard D. Row, undated (Box 32)
  - ROZHINKES MIT MANDLEN, by A. Goldfaden, arranged by Henry Lefkowitch, undated (Box 32)
  - RUMANIA, RUMANIA, arranged by Sholom Secunda, melody and words by Aaron Lebedeff, undated (Box 32)
  - RUMPEL-STILTS-KIN, words and music by Charles Tobias and Al Lewis, undated (Box 32)
  - SAPER VORRESTE DI CHE, G. Verdi, undated (Box 32)
  - THE SECOND MINUET, words by Aubrey Dowdon, music by Maurice Besly, undated (Box 32)
  - SE MIA GIOIA, by George Frideric Handel, 4 copies, undated (Box 32)
  - SERENADE, by Enrico Toselli, undated (Box 32)
  - SHABBAT MENUCHAII, by Abraham Ellestein, undated (Box 32)
  - THE SHADOW OF YOUR SMILE, lyrics by Paul Francis Weber, music by Johnny Mandel, undated (Box 32)
  - SHALOM, lyrics and music by Jerry Herman, 22 copies, undated (Box 32)
  - SHANGRI-LA, lyrics by Carl Sigman, music by Matt Malneck and Robert Maxwell, undated (Box 32)
  - SHEIN VI DI L'VONE, music by Joseph Rumshinsky, words by Chaim Tauber, undated (Box 32)
  - SHE NEVER TOLD HER LOVE, by Josef Haydn, undated (Box 32)
  - A SHIP WITHOUT A SAIL, lyrics by Lorenz Hart, music by Richard Rodgers, undated (Box 32)
  - SHIR ERES, by Moshe Wilensky, undated (Box 32)
  - THE SHORTEST DAY OF THE YEAR, words by Lorenz Hart, music by Richard Rodgers, undated (Box 32)
  - SIBONEY, by Ernesto Lecuona, lyrics by Dolly Morse, undated (Box 32)
  - SILVERIO, words and music by Agustin Lara, undated (Box 32)
  - SILVER MOON, words by Dorothy Donnelly, muric by Sigmund Romberg, undated (Box 32)
  - SILVER SONG, music by Douglas Moore, lyrics by John Latouche, undated (Box 32)
  - A SLEEPIN' BEE, lyrics by Truman Capote and Harold Arlen, music by Harold Arlen, undated (Box 32)
  - SLEEPY EYES, words by Tommie Connor, music by Harry Ralton, undated (Box 32)
  - SO IN LOVE, words and music by Cole Porter, undated (Box 32)
  - SOME DAY, words by Brian Hooker, music by Rudolf Friml, undated (Box 32)
  - SOMETHING TO LIVE FOR, words and music by Cole Porter, undated (Box 32)
  - SOMEWHERE, MY LOVE, lyrics by Paul Francis Webster, music by Maurice Jarre, undated (Box 32)
  - THE SONG IS YOU, lyrics by Oscar Hammerstein II, music by Jerome Kern, 2 copies, undated (Box 32)
  - SONG OF LOVE, by Julius Chajes, undated (Box 32)
  - A SONG OUT OF HEAVEN, musical arrangements and lyrics by Ann Ronell, undated (Box 32)
  - SOPHIA, words by Ira Gershwin, music by George Gershwin, 2 copies, undated (Box 32)
  - THE SPIDER AND THE FLY, by Thomas Waller, Andy Razaf, and J. C. Johnson, undated (Box 32)
  - A SPIRIT PASS'D BEFORE ME, music by Arthur H. Gutman, undated (Box 32)
  - THE SPRINGTIME COMETH, words by E. Y. Harburg, music by Sammy Fain, undated (Box 32)
  - STAIRWAY TO THE SEA, English lyrics by Albert A. Beach, music by Giuseppe Cioffi, undated (Box 32)
  - THE STAR, by James H. Rogers, undated (Box 32)
  - STARS IN MY EYES, words by Dorothy Fields, music by Fritz Kreisler, undated (Box 32)
  - THE STARS REMAIN, words by Henry Myers, music by Jay Gorney, undated (Box 32)
  - A STAR WAS HIS CANDLE, music by Teresa Del Riego, undated (Box 32)
  - STAY, words by Stephen Sondheim, music by Richard Rodgers, 2 copies, undated (Box 32)
  - A STRANGE LONELINESS, by Robert Burke and Sammy Mysels, undated (Box 32)
  - STRINGBEAN BOY, words by Don Raye, music by Gene De Paul, undated (Box 32)
  - SUMMER STARS, by Elinor Remick Warren, undated (Box 32)
  - SUMMERTIME, music by George Gershwin, lyrics by DuBose Heyward and Ira Gershwin, 2 copies, undated (Box 32)
  - THE SURREY WITH THE FRINGE ON TOP, music by Richard Rodgers, lyrics by Oscar Hammerstein II, undated (Box 32)
  - SWEET BEGINNING, words and music by Leslie Bricusse and Anthony Newley, undated (Box 32)
  - THE SWEETEST SONG IN THE WORLD, words and music by Harry Parr-Davies, 2 copies, undated (Box 32)
  - THE SWEETEST SOUNDS, words and music by Richard Rodgers, undated (Box 32)
  - SWEETHEARS, by Victor Herbert, undated (Box 32)
  - THE SYMPHONY, by Henry Sachs, undated (Box 32)
  - TAKE THE MOMENT, words by Stephen Sondheim, music by Richard Rodgers, 2 copies, undated (Box 32)
  - A TASTE OF HONEY, words by Ric Marlow, music by Bobby Scott, undated (Box 32)
  - TAWNY DAYS, by Elinor Remick Warren, undated (Box 32)
  - TEACH ME TONIGHT, words by Sammy Cahn, music by Gene De Paul, undated (Box 32)
  - TELL ME, LOVELY SHEPHERD, arranged by Elizabeth Poston, undated (Box 32)
  - THANK YOU SO MUCH, words by Stephen Sondheim, music by Richard Rodgers, 2 copies, undated (Box 32)
  - THAT'S WHAT IT IS TO BE YOUNG, words and music by Leslie Bricusse and Anthony Newley, undated (Box 32)
  - THEME OF THE QUIET MAN, words and music by Richard Farrelly, undated (Box 32)
  - THEN CAME THE RAIN, words by Charlie Tobias, music by Oscar Levant, undated (Box 32)
  - THERE'S NOTHING LIKE AN OLD FASHIONED WALTZ, music by Sam H. Stept, words by Ned Washington, undated (Box 32)
  - THE TICKLE TOE, lyrics by Otto Harbach, music by Louis A. Hirsch, undated (Box 32)
  - THEY DIDN'T BELIEVE ME, words by Herbert Reynolds, music by Jerome Kern, undated (Box 32)
  - THIS DREAM, words and music by Leslie Bricusse and Anthony Newley, undated (Box 32)
  - THIS IS THE LIFE, lyrics by Lee Adams, music by Charles Strouse, undated (Box 32)
  - THIS NIGHT, words by Gus Kahn, music by Harry Warren, undated (Box 32)
  - A THOUSAND AND ONE NIGHTS, words and music by Howard Leland, undated (Box 32)
  - A THOUSAND BEAUTIFUL THINGS, words by Richard Corrin, music by Haydn Wood, undated (Box 32)
  - TILL, words by Carl Sigman, music by Charles Danvers, undated (Box 32)
  - TIME ON MY HANDS, words by Harold Adamson and Mack Gordon, music by Vicnent Youmans, undated (Box 32)
  - TO BE ALONE WITH YOU, lyrics by Sidney Michaels, music by Mark Sandrich Jr., undated (Box 32)
  - TO BE SUNG UP ON A SUMMER NIGHT ON THE WATER, by Frederick Delius, undated (Box 32)
  - TOMORROW SINGS, words by S. A. DeWitt, music by Jacques Wolfe, undated (Box 32)
  - TOO LONG AT THE FAIR, words and music by Billy Barnes, undated (Box 32)
  - TOVARICH, music by Mana-Zucca, lyrics by Ben M. Kaye, undated (Box 32)
  - TREES, by Oscar Rasbach, undated (Box 32)
  - THE TRYST, by Jean Sibelius, undated (Box 32)
  - TUM-BALALAIKA, lyrics by Stanley L. Lionel, music by Henry Lefkowitch, undated (Box 32)
  - TURN AROUND, by Malvina Reynolds, Allen Greene, and Harry Belafonte, undated (Box 32)
  - THE TURNING TIDE, lyrics by Del Arden, music by Del Arden and Stewart Wille, undated (Box 32)
  - TWO BY TWO, words by Stephen Sondheim, music by Richard Rodgers, 2 copies, undated (Box 32)
  - TWO DREAMS GOT TOGETHER, words and music by Cliff Friend and Dave Franklin, undated (Box 32)
  - TWO FOOLS IN LOVE, by Fred Fisher and Stella Unger, undated (Box 32)
  - TWO LITTLE SHOES, by Mana-Zucca, undated (Box 32)
  - THE UMBRELLA MAN, words and music by James Cavanaugh, Vincent Rose, and Harry Stock, 2 copies, undated (Box 32)
  - UNA VOCE POCO, G. Rossini, arranged by Estelle Liebling, 2 copies, undated (Box 33)
  - UNDER PARIS SKIES, English words by Kim Gannon, music by Hubert Giraud, 2 copies, undated (Box 33)
  - UNDER THE BRIDGES OF PARIS, English lyrics by Dorcas Cochran, music by Vincent Scotto, undated (Box 33)
  - UNDER THE GREENWOOD TREE, by Douglas Moore, undated (Box 33)
  - TWO NIGHT SONGS, accompaniment by John Alden Carpenter, undated (Box 32)
  - UNLESS, by Mana-Zucca, undated (Box 33)
  - UNTIL SUNRISE, words and music by Jack Wolf Fine, Marie Moss and Will Collins, undated (Box 33)
  - UNTIL THE STARS FALL DOWN, words and music by Walter Donaldson, undated (Box 33)
  - UNVEIL YOUR EYES, words by David W. Guion and Clark Harrington, music by David W. Guion, undated (Box 33)
  - USK, music by Alan Thomas, undated (Box 33)
  - USE YOUR IMAGINATION, lyrics and music by Cole Porter, 2 copies, undated (Box 33)
  - THE VAGABOND KING WALTZ, words by Brian Hooker, music by Rudolf Friml, undated (Box 33)
  - VARNISHKES, music setting by Harry Anik, undated (Box 33)
  - THE VARSITY DRAG, words and music by B. G. De Sylva, Lew Brown and Ray Henderson, undated (Box 33)
  - VELVET PEOPLE, music by Ernst Bacon, undated (Box 33)
  - VERGEBLICHES STANDCHEN, Johannes Brahms, 2 copies, undated (Box 33)
  - VIENI, VIENI, lyrics by Geo. Koger and H. Varna, music by Vincent Scotto, undated (Box 33)
  - VILIA, words by Adrian Ross, music by Franz Lehar, 3 copies, undated (Box 33)
  - VIRGINIA, music by Alan Thomas, undated (Box 33)
  - VIRGINIA DON'T GO TOO FAR, lyrics by B.G. De Sylva, music by George Gershwin, undated (Box 33)
  - VOCALISE, by Wilbur Chenoeth, undated (Box 33)
  - VOCALISE, by S. Rachmaninoff, undated (Box 33)
  - VOCI DI PRIMAVERA, Johann Strauss, arranged by Estelle Liebling, undated (Box 33)
  - VOCI DI PRIMAVERA, Johann Strauss, undated (Box 33)